+55 61 99836-2112 (this number will change soon) arturcmjr@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/arturcmjr github.com/arturcmjr

# **ARTUR JUNIOR**

# **Summary**

Full stack developer with experience in all stages of the development cycle for web projects. Practical knowledge of numerous modern technologies. Focused on front-end lately yet can work perfectly with back-end. Visualizes the whole thing from the user's perspective to come up with ideas and solutions for possible problems.

## **Skill Highlights**

#### **Soft Skills**

- Fast learner
- Self-starter
- Creative
- Critical thinking

#### **Hard Skills**

- Angular
- .NET
- DevOps
- API integration

### **Experience**

Game Developer - 05/2017 to 11/2018

Roundstars, Brasilia, Brazil

- Worked on developing single-player and multiplayer board games. Coding core mechanism, search algorithms and bots Als. I've also designed interface for those games.
- Worked mainly with Unity and C# for game development. There I could also help with the creation of an API for a small social media.

**Designer** - 12/2018 to 10/2020

ADRA Brasil, Brasilia, Brazil

- Created art for fundraising campaigns for crises, design reports, and presentation slides with Photoshop, Illustrator, and other design software.
- There, I had the opportunity to develop a system to help to control the hot meals given to Venezuelan refugees.

Web Developer - 10/2020 to 09/2022

Adven.Tech, Remote, Brazil

- Worked developing web apps as a stock management, event, e-commerce and other systems on client demand. I also helped to migrate legacy systems to modern technologies.
- Written clean and scalable code for the back and front end. Worked with popular technologies such as Angular, React, .NET, C#, SQL and others.

### **Education**

- Graduation on Game Development 2018, IESB, Brasília, Brazil.
- Post-graduation at System Analysis and Development 2022, Descomplica, Remote.
- Post-graduation at Mobile Development 2022, Descomplica, Remote.